https://merulli.com/privacy-policy/

This blog’s publisher values the privacy of their Web/blog site viewers. Any of the following personal information that may be made available to the publisher when browsing or navigating the site shall be kept confidential:
First and last name
Company, home, postal or other physical address
Other contact information, for example, telephone number, fax number, email address, and other similar information
Title or position in a company or an organization
Occupation
Industry
Personal interests
Any other information needed to provide a service you requested
Examples of scenarios where our visitors provide their personal information include, but may not be limited, to:
Emailing, calling or communicating with the publisher.
Posting a question or comment through the site.
Requesting literature.
Registering to attend a seminar or any event.
Participating in an online survey.
Requesting inclusion in an email or other mailing list.
Submitting an entry for a contest or other promotions.
Logging in to the site, thus requiring a user name and/or a password.
Any other business-related reason.
The blog’s publisher provides you the opportunity to agree or decline to give your personal information via the Internet. The publisher will inform you of the purpose for the collection and does not intend to transfer your personal information to third parties without your consent, except under the limited conditions described under the discussion entitled “Information Sharing and Disclosure” below.
Domain Information Collection
The publisher may collect domain information to enable us to analyze how our visitors use this site. This data enables us to become more familiar with which people visit our site, how often they visit, and what parts of the site they visit most often. The publisher uses this information to improve its Web-based offerings. This information is collected automatically and requires no action on your part.
Use of Cookies and Tracking User Traffic
Some pages on this site may use “cookies”—small files that the site places on your hard drive for identification purposes. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID to track the pages visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. These files are used for site registration and customization the next time you visit us.
Some parts of the site may also use cookies to track user traffic patterns. The publisher does this in order to determine the usefulness of our Web site information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information. Please note that cookies cannot read data off of your hard drive. Your Web browser may allow you to be notified when you are receiving a cookie, giving you the choice to accept it or not. If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our Web site, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, By not accepting cookies, some pages may not fully function and you may not be able to access certain information on this site.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Your personal information is never shared without your permission, except under conditions listed below:
Consenting to share your information to a third party service provider working on our behalf to serve you.
Requiring us to provide you with a product or service.
The blog publisher will also disclose your personal information, if required to do so by law, or in urgent circumstances, to protect personal safety, the public or our sites.
Internet Security
The blog publisher strives to protect your personal information; however, we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters
Protecting the Privacy of Children
Children under 13 years old are not the target audience for our Web site. To protect their privacy, the blog publisher prohibits the solicitation of personal information from these children.
Links to Third Party Sites
This site may contain links to other sites. The blog publisher does not share your personal information with those Web sites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
The blog publisher reserves the right to change, modify or update this policy at any time without notice. Any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information will be posted on this site.
If you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please email us at the contact information on the site.
Download full privacy policy
Search for:
Clinic Hours & Location509 Olive Way #1658 Seattle, WA 98101
206-388-33499:30-6:00 Tuesday-Friday
10:00-3:00 Saturday
Sign Up Get Health Tips & Birthday Bonus
Latest Posts: MERULLI ACUPUNCTURE & WELLNESSNovember Wellness Promo!
Clinic Updates & Insurance
ConnectView merulliacupuncture’s profile on FacebookView merulli’s profile on TwitterView merulli’s profile on InstagramView desireemerulli’s profile on LinkedIn © 1998-2020 Desiree Merulli, L.Ac., EAMP, RYT Disclaimer Privacy Policy
